Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 71st Session, 1957-1991; 6
  - House Bills, 1987-1990; 4
    - Absentee Voting/Extended Voting: H.B. 344, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Aging/Long-Term Care Ombudsman: H.B. 541/S.B. 426, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture, Financial Assistance to Agriculture Businesses: H.B. 1111, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Bingo: H.B. 2260, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Bingo: H.B. 2260, Transcript, 1989 May (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Board of Licensure for Nursing Home Administrators: H.B. 312, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Child Pornography: H.B. 377, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - Conveyance of Property in Henderson County: H.B. 2404, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - County Judge or Commissioner Duties: H.B. 3012, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - Criminal Justice System Reform: H.B. 2335, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 22)
    - Dallas County Improvement District: H.B. 52, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 23)
    - Dallas County Improvement District: H.B. 3179, 1989 (Box 195, Folder 24)
    - Education: H.B. 1, Committee Substitute Comparison (1 of 3), 1990 May 8 (Box 195, Folder 25)
    - Education: H.B. 1, Committee Substitute Comparison (2 of 3), 1990 May 8 (Box 195, Folder 26)
    - Education: H.B. 1, Committee Substitute Comparison (3 of 3), 1990 May 8 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Education: H.B. 1, Comparative District Listing, 1990 May 8 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Election Candidates: H.B. 612, 1987 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Electric Utilities Purchase from Solid Waste Facilities: H.B. 2208, 1987 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Executive Branch Governing Boards, Official Minutes Content: H.B. 1506, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Henderson County Municipal Water Authority: H.B. 1606, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider: H.B. 2085 (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider: H.B. 2085 (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Texas National Research Laboratory Commission: H.B. 1909, 1987 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Inmate Drug and Alcohol Recovery: H.B. 817, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Justice Salaries: H.B. 101, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - McLennan County Courts: H.B. 3148, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Medicaid Cap: H.B. 318/S.B. 97, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Medigap: H.B. 116, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Medigap: H.B. 672 (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Medigap: H.B. 672 (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Municipal Park Property: H.B. 3158, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Non-Profit Self-Insurance: H.B. 721, 1989 (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Police and Fire Public Retirement Systems: H.B. 3175, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Political Party Conventions: H.B. 2524, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Prisoner of War Recognition Day: H.B. 404 and S.B. 119, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Public Education Appropriations: H.B. 1, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Real Estate Appraisal: H.B. 200, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Red Cross Blood Banks: H.B. 143, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Research Papers of the Joint Select Committee on Workers’ Compensation Insurance, 1988 October (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Sales and Use Tax: H.B. 2064, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - School Dropouts: H.B. 1010 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - School Dropouts: H.B. 1010 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - School and Junior College District Trustee Candidates: H.B. 377, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - State Licensing Agencies: H.B. 2363, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - State Sales Tax Rate Increase: H.B. 150, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Surplus and Salvage Property Sale to Rural and Volunteer Fire Departments: S.B. 452, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Steroids Regulation: H.B. 1507, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Teague Hospital District: H.B. 1168, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Texas National Research Laboratory Commission: S.B. 1428, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Texas Partnership and Scholarship Program: H.B. 86, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Texas State Technical Institute Fire Damage Repair: H.B. 1497, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Utilities, Telecommunications: H.B. 174, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Western Hill County Hospital District: H.B. 3174, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Workers Compensation Bill, House Committee Report: H.B. 1, 1989 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Workers Compensation H.B. 1, Joint Select Committee Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Workers Compensation, Joint Select Committee Findings, 1988-1989 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - House Resolutions, 1987-1990; 5
    - Economics, Texas Growth Fund: H.J.R. 5, 1987-1988 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Lieutenant Governor and State Office Salaries: H.J.R. 102, 1988-1989 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Poet Laureate of Texas: H.C.R. 143, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Texas Products and Business Financing: H.J.R. 51, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Topical, 1957-1991; 6
    - Abortion, 1986-1988 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Abortion (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Abortion (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Abortion, Statistics, 1986-1987 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, Family Land Heritage Program, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, Proposition 3, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture, Uranium Industry, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Appointments and Nominations (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Appointments and Nominations (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Appointments and Nominations, Decisions Past and Present, 1957-1990 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Appointments and Nominations, Regulations, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Auto Insurance, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Automobiles, Motor Vehicle Warranties, or Lemon Law, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Bingo, News Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Budget Execution, 1989 November (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Chiropractic, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Chiropractic (1 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Chiropractic (2 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Chiropractic, Board of Examiners, 1983-1988 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Chiropractic, Board of Examiners, 1986-1988 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Chiropractic, Request for Legislative Appropriations FY 1990-1991, 1988 October (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - College Opportunity Act, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller’s News Summary, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Department of Labor and Standards, Sunset Advisory Staff Report, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Dyslexia, 1988-1990 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Economic Development, 1989-1990 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Economics, East Texas, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Education, Hardesty Firing, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Education, Hardesty Firing, 1988-1990 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Education, Hardesty Firing, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Education, Higher Education, Research, 1989 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Education, Management Training, East Texas Research and Development, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Education, Speech Prep, 1987-1990 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Education, Texas Learning Technology Group, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Elderly and Aging, 1986-1989 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Elderly and Aging, Board and Care Homes, 1989-1990 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Election, Absentee Voting Records, 1984-1988 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - “English-Only”, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - “English-Only”, 1988-1989 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - General, Speeches and Speech Research, 1985-1989 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Growth Fund, 1989 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Health, AIDS, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Health, Alzheimer’s Information, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Appointments and Notes, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Peer Review, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, Texas Medical Association, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Hearing, 1986-1988 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, News Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners, News Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Public Hearing, 1987-1988 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Reports and Reviews, 1987, undated (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Reports and Reviews, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Health, Consumer’s Union, Medigap Insurance Information, 1987-1988 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Health, Consumer’s Union Packet, Medigap Reform, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Health, Elderwatch Long-Term Care Demonstration Project, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Health, General, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Health, Gray Panthers, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Health, Health Department Review, 1984-1988 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Health, Hunger and Nutrition and Indigent Healthcare, 1984-1988 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Health, Long-Term Health Care Proposals Notebook, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Health, Malpractice Testimonies, Board of Medical Examiners, 1985-1987 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Health, Malpractice Testimonies, Board of Medical Examiners, 1986-1988 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Health, Medicaid, 1986-1988 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Health, Medicaid, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Health, Medicaid, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Health, Medicaid Cap, S.B. 97 Info, 1988-1990 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Health, Medicaid Expansion Correspondence, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Health, Medicaid S.B. 298 Provisions Correspondence and Notes, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Health, Medical Assistance Liens S.B. 298, Edwards Correspondence, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Health, Medical Practice Act Amendments, 1987-1988 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Health, Medigap Resources (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Health, Medigap Resources (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Health, National Health Care, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Health, Nursing Home Status, 1987-1988, undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Health, Rural Healthcare, 1986-1989 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Health, Rural Healthcare, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Health, Rural Healthcare, Speech Preparation, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Liability Survey Study, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Nursing Home Reform, 1987-1988 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Nursing Home Standards (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Nursing Home Standards (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Proposals (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Proposals (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Proposals (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Health, Special Task Force on the Future of Long-Term Health Care, Testimonies and Report, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Health, State Board of Medical Examiners Admission, 1988-1989 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Health, Texas Department of Corrections, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Health, Texas Health Care Association, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Health, United People for Better Nursing Home Care, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Health and Human Services, Medically Fragile Children, 1988 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Health Issues, Speech Research (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Health Issues, Speech Research (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Health Services, Intermediate Care Facility for Mentally Retarded (ICF-MR) (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Health Services, Intermediate Care Facility for Mentally Retarded (ICF-MR) (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Health Services, Intermediate Care Facility for Mentally Retarded (ICF-MR) (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Health Services, Mental Health and Mental Retardation (MHMR), Prospective Payment Program (PPP) funding (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Health Services, Mental Health and Mental Retardation (MHMR), Prospective Payment Program (PPP) funding (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Health Services, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Services for the Mentally Ill (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Health Services, Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Services for the Mentally Ill (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Health Services, Medicaid Reimbursement to Nursing Homes, 1987-1990 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Health Services, Nurse Assistant Training Program, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Health Services, Senate Sub-Committee, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Health Services, Senate Sub-Committee, Long-Term Care (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Health Services, Senate Sub-Committee, Long-Term Care (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Higher Education, Speech and Speech Preparation, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Higher Education in South Texas Report, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Agriculture, 1987-1990 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Chet Edwards’s Speeches and Notes, 1985-1988 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Entrepreneurship, 1983-1988 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, General, 1987-1989 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, General Speeches and Notes, 1984-1989 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, High Technology in Texas, 1983-1988 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Higher Education, 1986-1988 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Technology Business Development, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Texas A&M University Programs, 1989, undated (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, TIINS, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Texas Innovation Information Network System (TIINS) (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Texas Innovation Information Network System (TIINS) (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Texas Learning Technology Level, 1986-1988 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider (1 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider (2 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider, 1990 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider Environmental Impact Statement, 1990 August (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider and Texas National Research Laboratory Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Super Collider and Texas National Research Laboratory Commission, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Technology Industry Legislative Task Force Report, 1989 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Homelessness, 1985-1988 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Homelessness, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Homelessness, 1988-1989 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Homelessness, Health and Human Services Coordinating Council, Final Report, 1985 October (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Homelessness, Hunger and Nutrition Reports, 1984-1988 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Homelessness, Living in the Gray Zone: Health Care Needs of Homeless Persons, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Homestead, 1989-1990, undated (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Human Services, Ad Hoc Committee Meetings on Medical Liens, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Human Services, House Research Organization, Medicaid Reimbursement Liens Brief, 1988 March 28 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Human Services, Medicaid, Ad Hoc Committee Report and Statement, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Human Services, Medicaid Information and Briefing, S.B. 298, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Human Services, Missing Child Procedures, Sabat, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Human Services, State Budget, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, 1986-1989 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Insurance, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Insurance, Antitrust Suit, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, State Board Investigation (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, State Board Investigation (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, State Board Investigation (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Insurance Information, 1989-1990 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Jail Populations and Financing, 1980-1990 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Law Enforcement Personnel Solicitations, H.B. 921 and S.B. 427, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Law Enforcement S.B. 427 and H.B. 921 Support, 1989 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Advisory Group (1 of 2), 1988, undated (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, Advisory Group (2 of 2), 1988, undated (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Local Measured Service, Centel Corporation Rate Information, 1984-1988 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service, General Telephone and Electronics, Continental Telecom, Rates Information, 1983-1988 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Local Measured Service, Potential Impacts of LMS on State Government, 1988 March (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Revolving Door, 1985-1989 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Revolving Door, 1988-1989 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Revolving Door Legislation, 1989 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Senate Subcommittee on Health Services, 1989 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Long-Term Care, Speech Research, 1988 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Long-Term Health Care, Special Task Force, 1988 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Long-Term Health Care, Special Task Force, 1988 August-September (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Lottery, 1989, undated (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - McLennan County, Tenth Court of Appeals, 1989 (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Medicaid Program Statistics, 1986 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Medigap, A Shopper’s Guide to Medicare Supplement Insurance in Texas, 1989 July (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Medigap Research, 1978 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Medigap Resources, 1988-1989 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Navarro College, Information, 1987 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Navarro College, Information, 1987-1988 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Navarro College, Senior Citizens Programs Review (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Navarro College, Senior Citizens Programs Review (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Navarro College, Special Audit Report, 1988 May (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Office of State-Federal Relations, 1989 February-March (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Police Solicitations Bill Information (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Police Solicitations Bill Information (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Police Solicitations Bill Information (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Police Solicitations Bill Information and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Public Utility Commission, Houston Lighting and Power, 1988 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Radiation (1 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Radiation (2 of 2), 1985-1989 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Ridge v. Verity, Census Bureau, 1988 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Solid Waste, Ellis County, Eagle Consolidated Inc. (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Solid Waste, Ellis County, Eagle Consolidated Inc. (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Solid Waste, Palmer/Ennis, 1987-1988 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Conference (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Southwest Conference (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Conference, Articles, 1990 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Southwest Conference, Constitutional Law Research (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Southwest Conference, Constitutional Law Research (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Southwest Conference, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Small Business, Speech Preparation Notebook, 1989 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - State Offices and Salaries, 1986-1988 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - State Treasury’s System for Collateralizing State Deposits, Audit Report, 1988 July (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Sunset Advisory Commission, Recommendations to the Governor and Members of the 71st Legislature of Texas, 1989 February (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Super Tuesday, Review, 1988 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Superconducting Super Collider, Speeches and News Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Taxes, 1990 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Texas A&M University System, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Texas Alliance for Minorities in Engineering, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Texas Economy, 1990 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Texas Education Agency, Sunset Advisory Staff Report, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Texas Funeral Service Commission, W.H. Littles Case, 1988-1990 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Texas Learning Technology Group, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Texas Main Street Project, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Texas Silver-Haired Legislature, Health, Medicaid Eligibility Resolution, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Texas Silver-Haired Legislature, Resolutions, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Texas Silver-Haired Legislature, Health, Second Session Report, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Texas State Technical Institute, Senate Committee, 1990 July- August (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Texas State Technical Institute, Senate Committee, 1990 September (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Texas State Technical Institute Appropriations (1 of 2), 1987-1991 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Texas State Technical Institute Appropriations (2 of 2), 1987-1991 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Trucking Deregulation, 1986-1987 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Trucking Deregulation (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Trucking Deregulation (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Articles and Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Articles and Statements, 1986-1989 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Articles, Statements, and Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Information, 1986-1988 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Intrastate Trucking in Texas: The Impact of Common Carrier Trucking Deregulation, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Trucking Deregulation, Railroad Commission of Texas, Staff Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Utilities, 1989 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Utilities, AOS Amended Recommended Memo, Florida (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Utilities, AOS Amended Recommended Memo, Florida (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Utilities, AOS Articles, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Utilities, AOS Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Utilities, AOS Reports (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, AOS Reports (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Central Corporation and Teleservices Corporation, Reports and Rates, 1987-1988 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Utilities, Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT), 1988 (Box 216, Folder 9)